<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!DOCTYPE module PUBLIC "-//NetBeans//DTD Autoupdate Module Info 2.3//EN"
        "http://www.netbeans.org/dtds/autoupdate-info-1_0.dtd">

<module codenamebase="org.icefaces.module.auctionMonitor"
        homepage="http://www.icefaces.org/"
        distribution="http://localhost:8080/icefaces_auctionMonitor_1_7_0.jar"
        license="MPLorLGPL"
        downloadsize="11932910"
        needsrestart="false"
        moduleauthor="ICEsoft Technologies, Inc."
        releasedate="2008/05/21">

    <manifest OpenIDE-Module="org.icefaces.module.auctionMonitor/1"
              OpenIDE-Module-Display-Category="ICEfaces"
              OpenIDE-Module-Implementation-Version="20080521"
              OpenIDE-Module-Long-Description="Auction Monitor is an ICEfaces web application that simulates an online auction.  It demonstrates the benefits of Ajax Push and component-based development."
              OpenIDE-Module-Module-Dependencies=""
              OpenIDE-Module-Name="ICEfaces Auction Monitor"
              OpenIDE-Module-Requires=""
              OpenIDE-Module-Short-Description="ICEfaces Auction Monitor"
              OpenIDE-Module-Specification-Version="1.7.0"
              Module-Type="APPLICATION"
              Target-Container="sjsas91beta"/>

    <license name="MPLorLGPL">
        <![CDATA[ Version: MPL 1.1/GPL 2.0/LGPL 2.1

"The contents of this file are subject to the Mozilla Public License
Version 1.1 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in
compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
http://www.mozilla.org/MPL/

Software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS"
basis, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
License for the specific language governing rights and limitations under
the License.

The Original Code is ICEfaces 1.5 open source software code, released
November 5, 2006. The Initial Developer of the Original Code is ICEsoft
Technologies Canada, Corp. Portions created by ICEsoft are Copyright (C)
2004-2006 ICEsoft Technologies Canada, Corp. All Rights Reserved.

Contributor(s): _____________________.

Alternatively, the contents of this file may be used under the terms of
the GNU Lesser General Public License Version 2.1 or later (the "LGPL"
License), in which case the provisions of the LGPL License are
applicable instead of those above. If you wish to allow use of your
version of this file only under the terms of the LGPL License and not to
allow others to use your version of this file under the MPL, indicate
your decision by deleting the provisions above and replace them with
the notice and other provisions required by the LGPL License. If you do
not delete the provisions above, a recipient may use your version of
this file under either the MPL or the LGPL License."

]]>
    </license>
</module>